const englishPronounciationQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following words is pronounced with a silent 'k' at the beginning?",
    options: ["Knight", "Know", "Kangaroo", "Knife"],
    correct_option: "Knight",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the correct pronunciation of the word 'schedule' in American English?",
    options: ["Sked-yool", "Shed-yool", "Sked-yoo-ul", "Shed-yoo-ul"],
    correct_option: "Sked-yool",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following words has stress on the second syllable?",
    options: ["Photograph", "Photography", "Photogenic", "Photocopier"],
    correct_option: "Photography",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you pronounce the 'th' sound in the word 'clothes'?",
    options: [
      "Like 'klothes'",
      "Like 'zlothes'",
      "Like 'slothes'",
      "Like 'tlothes'",
    ],
    correct_option: "Like 'zlothes'",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the correct pronunciation of the letter 'H' in the word 'hour'?",
    options: [
      "Silent, like 'our'",
      "Pronounced, like 'h-our'",
      "Pronounced, like 'hour'",
      "Silent, like 'hour'",
    ],
    correct_option: "Silent, like 'our'",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following words has a long vowel sound in the first syllable?",
    options: ["Paper", "Pizza", "Pencil", "People"],
    correct_option: "People",
  },
  {
    question: "How is the 'ed' ending pronounced in the word 'started'?",
    options: ["Like 'ed'", "Like 'd'", "Like 't'", "Like 'id'"],
    correct_option: "Like 'id'",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the correct stress pattern in the word 'information'?",
    options: [
      "In-fo-MAY-shun",
      "In-FO-ma-tion",
      "In-for-MA-tion",
      "In-for-ma-TION",
    ],
    correct_option: "In-fo-MAY-shun",
  },
  {
    question: "How is the 'ea' pronounced in the word 'bread'?",
    options: ["Like 'ee'", "Like 'eh'", "Like 'ae'", "Like 'ay'"],
    correct_option: "Like 'eh'",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the correct pronunciation of the word 'nuclear'?",
    options: ["Nuke-lee-ar", "New-klee-ar", "Noo-klee-ar", "Nyoo-klee-ar"],
    correct_option: "Noo-klee-ar",
  },
];
export default englishPronounciationQuestions;
